saptechnical.com 2014-11-22

# SAPTechnical.COM - Privacy

We know you take your privacy seriously. We don't collect details from you. We don't require cookies for you to operate the site (unless visiting a sponsors page). What comes in DOES NOT GET STORED ANYWHERE, unless you specifically request it like registering your resume or job with us.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

We don't collect personal information so we don't cover the dissemination of personal information. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SAPTechnical.COM does not own or control, or to people that SAPTechnical.COM does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

SAPTechnical.COM is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

**Links**

This Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that SAPTechnical.COM is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware of when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by SAPTechnical.COM Web sites.

**SAPTechnical.COM** **Staffing**

We do not directly contact individual members of our audience regarding SAPTechnical.COM Staffing opportunities unless they have requested that we do so by submitting their resume or applying for a position. We will not sell, loan, or otherwise distribute our resume database except as noted in Business Transfers.

**Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via any SAPTechnical.COM Web site, your information is protected both online and offline.

Your SAPTechnical.COM account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. Access to any user information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is heavily restricted within our company. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our system administrators) are granted access to personally identifiable information. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. In addition, the servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

If you have any questions about the security at our Web sites, you can send an email to [webmaster@saptechnical.com](mailto:webmaster@saptechnical.com) requesting further information.

**Business Transfers**

As we continue to develop our business, we might buy or sell businesses or business assets. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred assets. In the unlikely event that SAPTechnical.COM, Inc., sells SAPTechnical.COM, Inc., or one or more of its properties , user information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will make these changes available from our Homepage. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information we will notify users by way of an announcement on the home page.

**Newly added** :

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Contact Information

For additional information on privacy issues, please contact us by e-mail at [webmaster@saptechnical.com](mailto:webmaster@saptechnical.com)
